Guide to the Records of WNYU RG.39.5
New York University Archives
- Series V: Recorded Programs, 1968-1996; 20 Linear Feet in 14 record cartons, 3 LP boxes, 2 manuscript boxes, and 1 CD box.
  - New Afternoon Show: Roger Manning (Interview and Live), August 3, 1989 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0162)
  - New Afternoon Show: Rats of Unusual Size (Live and Interview), August 17, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0625)
  - New Afternoon Show: Winter Hours (Live, Interview), September 12, 1989 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0656, 39_5_0666, 39_5_0667)
  - New Afternoon Show: Cop Shoot Cop, September 28, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0309)
  - New Afternoon Show: Lubricated Goat, Halo of Flies, October 13, 1989 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0508)
    Duration: 00:16:50
  - New Afternoon Show: Baby Flame Head, October 27, 1989 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0186)
  - New Afternoon Show: Nikki Sudden, October 27, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0140)
  - New Afternoon Show: Screaming Blue Messiahs (Interview), November 2, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0150)
    The host of this episode is Kristin.
  - New Afternoon Show: Beme Seed, circa Decemer 1, 1989 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0008)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blixa Bargeld of Einstrzende Neubauten, December 28, 1989 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0219)
    The host of this episode is Ken Richards.
  - New Afternoon Show: Die Kreuzen (Interview), March 14, 1990 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0095)
  - New Afternoon Show: Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, Chris Reed, March 19 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0351)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blue Aeroplanes (Interview and Acoustic Set), April 4, 1990 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0237)
    The host of this episode is Lisa.
  - New Afternoon Show: Sundays (Interview), April 11, 1990 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0641)
  - New Afternoon Show: Scrawl, May 4, 1990 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0269)
  - New Afternoon Show: Reverb Motherfuckers (Interview), May 11, 1990 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0495, Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0670)
    Duration: 00:25:53
  - New Afternoon Show: Babes in Toyland, May 17, 1990 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0034)
  - New Afternoon Show: Blue Aeroplanes, June 11, 1990 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0369)
  - New Afternoon Show: Died Pretty (Live Acoustic Set and Interview), June 12, 1990 (Box 27, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0212)
  - New Afternoon Show: Sonic Youth, June 12, 1990 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0621)
  - New Afternoon Show: David Kilgour (Live), circa 1990s (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0398)
    The host of this episode is J. Connolly.
  - New Afternoon Show: Chickasaw Mudd Puppies (Live and Interview), July 16, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0346)
  - New Afternoon Show: Vertigo (Live, Interview), July 17, 1990 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0648)
  - New Afternoon Show: The 6 and Violence (Live), August 10, 1990 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0161)
  - New Afternoon Show: Charlatans UK, September 6, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0338)
  - New Afternoon Show: Nick Cave, with Lust, September 18, 1990 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0217)
  - New Afternoon Show: Toys Went Berserk, September 26, 1990 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0599)
  - New Afternoon Show: Tackhead (Interview), October 31, 1990 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0581)
  - New Afternoon Show: Roger Manning (Interview and Live), November 5, 1990 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0051)
  - New Afternoon Show: Jazz Butcher, November 13, 1990 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0192)
    The host of this episode is Ida.
  - New Afternoon Show: Smashing Pumpkins (Interview), February 11, 1991 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0304)
  - New Afternoon Show: Smashing Orange (Live), February 22, 1991 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0371)
  - New Afternoon Show: Harm Farm (Live, Interview), May 13, 1991 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0143)
  - New Afternoon Show: Uncle Wiggly, April 29, 1992 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0229)
  - New Afternoon Show: Gary Lucas, October 13, 1993 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0042)
  - New Afternoon Show: David Kilgour and Noel (Live), Undated (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0031)
  - New Afternoon Show: Husker Du, Undated (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0203)
  - New Afternoon Show: Splat Cat (Interview), Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0288)
    Audio reel 39_5_0288 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - New Afternoon Show: The Donner Party, Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0532)
  - New Afternoon Show: The Pixies (Live), Undated (Box 27, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0211, 39_5_0213)
  - The New Midnight Society: Kilkenny Cats (Live), Adrian Belew (Interview), July 17, 1989 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0294)
  - The New Midnight Society: White Trash (Live), July 18, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0296)
  - The New Midnight Society: White Zombie (Live), July 18, 1989 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0102)
  - The New Midnight Society: Day 3, July 19, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0627, Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0295)
    This recording includes Dangtrippers (Live), Snatches of Pink (Acoustic Set and Interview), False Prophets (Interview), and Marlene on the New Afternoon Show.
  - The New Midnight Society: False Prophets (Interview), Cows (Live Set and Interview), Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0293)
  - Radio Recess: Pressed Rat and Warthog, 1968 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0277)
    Story by Stuart Ritchie, Original by Ginger Baker
  - Radio Recess: Malvia Lanoue, May 16, 1994 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0185)
    Featuring the songs "One Revolution Under the Sun" and "The World is Yours"
  - Radio Recess Special: Richard Bartee, Undated (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0052, Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0577)
  - Radio Recess Voices: Tuxedo Junction, Waltzing Matilda, Undated (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0117)
  - Radio Recess Voices: We Are Family, Undated (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0241)
  - Radio Recess: Daniel Carlton, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0263)
  - Radio Recess: Richard Bartee, Undated (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0270)
  - Radio Recess: Yani Washington, Undated (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0624)
    Yani Washington tells two fables, "How Brer Alligator Met Trouble" and "How the Moon and the Sun Found Their Home in the Sky."
  - Rap This!: Cut Master and LL Cool J Contest, 1985-1986 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0517)
  - Rap This!: Kool Moe Dee (Interview), February 24, 1987 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0399)
    Duration: 00:32:07
  - Rap This!: LL Cool J (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0407)
    Duration: 00:19:33
    The host of this episode is P-Fine.
  - Rap This!: White Boys (Interview), Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0593, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0403)
    Duration: 00:16:56
  - Unheard: The Dictators (Interview), circa 1980s (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0501)
    The host of this episode is Evan Davies.
  - Unheard: Woofing Cookies, 1986 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0556)
  - Unheard: Das Furlines, November 13, 1986 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0530)
    Audio reel 39_5_0530 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Unheard: Carmaig DeForest (Live), July 16, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0333)
  - Unheard: Waxmen (Live Set, Interview), Hunting Accident (Interview), Antoinettes (Interview), March 3, 1988 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0592)
  - Unheard: Corvairs (Live Performance), April 14, 1988 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0001)
  - Unheard: Riff Kings (Interview), April 14, 1988 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0001)
  - Unheard: Gary Lucas (Live), May 26, 1988 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0061, Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0090)
  - Unheard: Zero, May 26, 1988 (Box 13, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0090)
  - Unheard: Hetch Hetchy (Live), June 2, 1988 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0347)
  - Unheard: The Proclaimers, February 23, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0308)
  - Unheard: Lovelies, March 2, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0202)
  - Unheard: Vital Music Roster, March 16, 1989 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0590)
    Featuring interviews and live sets with the Waxmen, Rats of Unusual Size, Braindrops, and Lysdexic.
  - Unheard: Kathy McCarty of Glass Eye (Interview and Live Set), March 30, 1989 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0067)
  - Unheard: Sarah McLachlan (interview), April 5, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0201)
  - Unheard: Two Nice Girls, May 18, 1989 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0569)
  - Unheard: Something Happens (Live and Interview), June 8, 1989 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0636)
  - Unheard: Purple Geezus, June 15, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0196)
  - Unheard: The Unsane (Live), August 3, 1989 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0564)
  - Unheard: Aquanettas (Live, Interview), September 28, 1989 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0528)
  - Unheard: Sleepyhead (Live), April 19, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0370, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0394)
    Duration: 00:23:09
    The host of this episode is Jen.
  - Unheard: Disposable God Squad (Live), October 4, 1990 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0541)
  - Unheard: Baby Tapeworm, October 18, 1990 (Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0006)
  - Unheard: Crisis (Live and Interview), March 14, 1994 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0387)
    Duration: 00:24:37
    Label includes commentary: "Crisis from NYC, not the UK punk band! Definitely obscene - 'Don't need your dick in me boy, but I can get it if I want it.'"
  - Unheard: Crisis (Live), March 17, 1994 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0665)
  - Unheard: Micheal Rouse, Tirez Tirez, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0598)
  - Unheard: Too Much Joy, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0575)
  - Tisch Hall Time Capsule Predictions, April 25, 1969 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0573)
  - Ramones, August 23, 1973 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0209)
    Featuring the songs "Rock n' Roll Radio," "I'm Affected," "Carbona Not Glue," "Rock n' Roll High School," and "Blitzkrieg Bop"
  - Fleshtones, May 29, 1980 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0373)
    Featuring the songs "Fascination," "Shadowline," and "I'm in with the Out Crowd." The hosts of this episode are J. Edwusken and Mike Dugan.
  - The Only Ones, July 25, 1980 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0326)
  - Blasters, March 19, 1982 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0180)
    Also aired on September 9, 1982
  - Gun Club (Interview), May 19, 1982 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0365, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0404)
    Duration: 00:22:52
  - Flipper, May 27, 1982 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0672)
    Songs performed include "Earthworm," "Love Canal," and "Ever."
  - Dead Kennedys, August 5, 1982 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0653)
  - Lords of the New Church, October 1, 1982 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0021)
  - Undertones, October 1, 1982 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0565)
    Featuring the songs "It's Going to Happen," "When Saturday Comes," and "God Go With You"
  - Chesterfield Kings, March 4, 1983 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0411)
    Audio reel 39_5_0411 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Let's Active, October 21, 1983 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0053)
  - In Good Faith, January 26, 1984 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0358)
  - Einsturzende Neubaten, March 16, 1984 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0318)
  - Sonic Youth, April 6, 1984 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0299)
  - The HeartBreakers, June 3, 1984 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0364)
    Featuring the songs "Can't Keep My Eyes on You," "Seven Day Weekend," and "Take a Chance (Nolan)"
  - Meat Puppets (Interview), October 26, 1984 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0178, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0386)
    Duration: 00:34:40
  - NYU Lecture Series: Econ/Health Care Symposium, January 21, 1985 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0066)
  - Dogmatics, February 15, 1985 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0149)
    Featuring the songs "MTV-OD," "Whipped," and "Good Looking Girls"
  - Del Fuegos, February 22, 1985 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0144)
  - Red Lorry Yellow Lorry, March 16, 1985 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0600)
    Air Date: April 12, 1985
  - NYU Lecture Series: Intelligence Operations, cont'd, April 4, 1985 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0066)
  - Sehnap, July 19, 1985 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0019)
  - Sonic Youth, Kim, January 9, 1986 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0132)
  - Angst, January 18, 1986 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0669)
  - Descendants, January 24, 1986 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0322)
  - Blixa Bargeld of Einsturzende Neubauten (Interview), May 29, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0502)
  - Blixa of E. Neubaten, May 29, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0057)
  - Petre Zoremba, "Love Delegation", July 10, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0044)
  - Funk it! Tomas Donker (Interview), August 3, 1986 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0230)
  - Ramones (Interview), August 27, 1986 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0173)
  - Easterhouse (Interview), September 8, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0077, Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0163)
  - Circle Jerks: Greg Morris and Keith Hientz, September 24, 1986 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0252)
  - Lone Cowboys/Bureaucrats, September 25, 1986 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0121)
  - Dumptruck and Marti Jones, October 10, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0050)
  - Don Dixon, October 28, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0073)
  - Afrika Bambaata, November 18, 1986 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0509)
    Duration: 00:23:01
  - Love Dolls, with Lust, November 19, 1986 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0045)
  - Kilkenny Cats, November 21, 1986 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0033)
  - Kill Kenny Katz, November 21, 1986 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0193)
  - Kraftwerk, R. Hutter, November 25, 1986 (Box 27, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0218)
    includes handwritten transcript of an interview with Kraftwerk
  - ESG (Interview), 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0060, Box 22, Cd 39_5_0388)
    Duration: 00:04:49
  - Kool Moe Dee, "Rap This", February 24, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0027)
  - Splatcats (Live), March 6, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0133)
  - Das Damen, April 9, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0529)
  - Kelly Charles, July 3, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0012)
    Reel includes another label listing Earshot: Sal Lo Curto and Chuck Yochim, December 8, 1981, and a WNBC recording from January 3, 1982
  - Exodus, July 14, 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0059)
  - Swans Acoustic Performance, July 20, 1987 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0512)
    Duration: 00:04:52
  - Warzone (Live), July 23, 1987 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0071)
  - 76% Uncertain (Live), September 3, 1987 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0566)
  - Criminal, September 16, 1987 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0352)
  - Hammerbrain (Live), September 17, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0138, Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0183)
  - Membranes (Live), September 24, 1987 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0119)
  - Push, Liquid Hips, October 5, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0257)
  - Social Decay, October 8, 1987 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0266)
  - Damage (Live), October 22, 1987 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0538, 39_5_0550, 39_5_0551)
  - Real Life (Remix), October 23, 1987 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0256)
  - Opal (Interview), Couch Flambeau (Live), circa November, 1987 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0323)
  - John White, "Victim", November 5, 1987 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0036)
    Smoothmix Productions, Geffen Records, Remixed and Re-edited by Jonathan Doncker and Chris Cullen.
  - Tony Terry (Interview), November 10, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0657)
  - Public Enemy Insane to the Brain Power Mix with D.J. White Lightning, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0633)
    Featuring "Don't Believe the Hype," "The Revolution Will Not Be Televised," Excerpts from Malcolm X Speeches, "Terminator X on the Age of Panic," "Louder Than a Bomb," "The Night of the Living Baseheads," "Cold Lampin With Flavor," and "Party for Your Right to Fight."
  - Bustin' Out, March 3, 1988 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0336, Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0156)
  - Breakdown (Live), March 10, 1988 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0337, Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0630)
  - Dramarama (Live acoustic and Interview), April 8, 1988 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0278)
  - Pedal Jets (Live), April 28, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0223)
  - Kid n' Play, De La Soul (Interview), circa June, 1988 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0114)
  - Downy Mildew (Live), June 7, 1988 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0531)
  - Mr. T Experience (Live), July 7, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0303)
  - Mucky Pup, Metallurgy, July 9, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0235)
  - The Bats (Live and Interview), Kiwisex, July 21, 1988 (Box 27, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0215)
  - David Peel on Plastic Tales from the Marshmallow Dimension (Live and Interview), July 25, 1988 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0298)
  - Reverb Motherfuckers (Live, Interview), September 2, 1988 (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0496)
    Duration: 00:32:08
  - Rigormortis, Metallurgy, October 11, 1988 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0246)
  - Raunch Hands, October 21, 1988 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0634)
  - Spit (Live), November 3, 1988 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0166)
  - Stevie Ray Vaughn on MTV Unplugged, circa 1989-1990 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0283)
    Songs performed include "Rude Mood," "Pride and Joy," and "Testify."
  - Pete Townshend, May 4, 1989 (Box 27, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0214, 39_5_0216, Box 10, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0220)
  - Shake 'Em On Down: World Famous Blue Jays, circa July, 1989 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0198)
  - Popealopes/Naked Raygun, July 17, 1989 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0070)
  - Swans Acoustic Set, July 20, 1989 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0134, 39_5_0139)
    Featuring the songs "I Remember Who You Are," "Can't Find My Way Home," "See No More," and "Goddamn the Sun."
  - The Radicts (Live), August 24, 1989 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0075)
  - Buzzcocks, November 10, 1989 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0316)
  - Henry Rollins, March 9, 1990 (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0206)
  - Shadows J Live Rap (Over the Power Jam), April 5, 1990 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0618)
  - Rifle Sport, April 12, 1990 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0259)
  - Nihilistics (Interview), November 29, 1990 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0367)
  - "McBroom's Zoo," McBloom Zoo Animals, Spring, 1991 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0152)
    Original Story by Syd Flieshmen, Adapted by Robin Johnson
  - Richard Linklater (Interview), July 1, 1991 (Box 11, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0018)
  - Gary Lukas and Jeff Buckley, March 12, 1992 (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0324)
  - "Spillin'" by George A. Sosa (Final Mix), April 10, 1992 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0620)
  - Breakdown, September 24, 1992 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0245)
  - Men Without Talent, Metallurgy, November 13, 1992 (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0153)
  - Peter Piper, Final Mix, February 12, 1993 (Box 17, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0221)
    By Mathew, Actress: Ameenah Kaplan
  - Eric Bogosian Interview for Matthew Finch, October 17, 1993 (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0525)
    The host of this episode is Aaron Goldman.
  - Robert Cray (Interview), November 17, 1993 (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0348)
    The host of this episode is Ryan Crisman.
  - "Moon Lake" Final Mix, circa Spring, 1994 (Box 18, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0274)
    Recorded with Ameenah Kaplan.
  - Satchmo's Gang, June 2, 1995 (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0128)
  - Latino Show - 3 Guitars with Vox, June 12, 1995 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0562)
  - Sabrina Cyrille, NYC Marathon, November 13, 1995 (Box 16, Fidelipac 39_5_0560)
  - Foley From Easter '96, circa 1996 (Box 12, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0062)
  - 4 TK Doors Mix, Feature, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0372)
    Featuring the songs "Got to Give it Up," "A Horse, Hotel, Patty, Bonanza, Native, I Never"
  - 7 Against Thebes "After Scary Halloween Thing", Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0545)
  - A Collegiate Christmas Carol, Pt. 2, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0355)
  - Afrika Bambaata (Interview), Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0521)
  - Altercation (Live), Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0553)
  - Andy Sex Gang, Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0544)
  - Auto Pilot, Bullet Lavolta, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0334)
  - Billy Idol (Interview), Undated (Box 22, Cd 39_5_0505)
  - Billy Idol (Live), Undated (Box 21, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0522)
  - Brian Brain, Undated (Box 15, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0176)
  - Bush Tetras (Live), Undated (Box 16, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0639)
    Songs performed include "Too Many Creeps," "Snakes Crawl," and "Taste Like the Tropics."
    Audio reel 39_5_0639 was identified as moldy in December, 2022. This item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, contact the Preservation Department immediately. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Buzzcocks, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0314)
  - Captain Sensible, Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0339)
  - Chemical Waste (Live), Undated (Box 20, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0343, 39_5_0354)
  - Circle Jerks, Undated (Box 19, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0302)
  - Closer Look, Undated (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0563)
  - Crazy F. Man Presents Deep Vibes, "A Brand New Day", Undated (Box 14, Quarter inch audio reel 39_5_0146)
    Recorded by Rey D. Featuring Ron Gilles on guitar, Alfredo Romero on piano.